<resources>
    <string name="app_name">INSES</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="GOOGLE_MAP_KEY">AIzaSyD66B_rCcRh91U1xiB_43iRBljEc4QHnio</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="search_for_services">search for services</string>
    <string name="answer">Go to home and select the service you want to book. Add any item to your cart, select the address where you want the service and schedule it according to your convenience. After that, just pay and book the service and we will take care of the rest.</string>
    <string name="about">We INSES are providing an Electrical and Plumbing Services located in Madurai, Tamil Nadu. Basically Inses will give a humorous preferable for Madurai People mainly Villapuram, Nilayur, Thirupparamkunram, Thirunagar, Anna Nagar, Four Masi Streets etc., Our Installation and Service divisions provide emergency and routing preventive maintenance to end users of our plumbing projects and to the wide range of business related customers. Our Flexible and Professional approach enables our clients to access a full range of services depending on their needs. Our elegant approach to our work means that projects are completed without hindrance to our clients: we take this very contentiously. Once a project is completed, we follow up with the client on further servicing levels.</string>
    <string name="vision">We provide clients with professional fast and reliable solutions that best suit and service their needs. We are often commended by clients for the friendly and client centric approach of our team members. INSES was selected as our Electrical and Plumbing based on a blend of their eminent experience, Skill Sets, Track Record, passion for plumbing and Electrical Winding were the ability to truly engage with our clients. This results we offer is eventually proven through our excellent services and continued word of mouth referrals we receive.</string>
    <string name="mission">To provide clients anonymously with quality products and excellent services that exceed customer expectation in this Electrical and Plumbing Industry to create long term relationships with our insightful clients. Basically Quality service is a non negotiable at INSES. Many of our clients know our review already. They know we will be there on time and we will sort out their electrical and plumbing issues right first time round.</string>
    <string name="industries">We have experience assisting the following range of clients / Industries with divergent Electrical and Plumbing requirements.

Commercial Industry
Residential Homes
Estate and Rental Agents
Industrial Industry
Hospitality Industry
Construction Departments</string>
    <string name="bussinessCategories">INSES significant advantage is its accessible pools of in house skills available for the successful management and maintenance of all aspects of Electrical and Plumbing Services. We always think in terms of solutions and their implementation in the systems.

Plumbing Services
Electrical Works
Installation
Maintenance
LED Tv
New Connection
Painting</string>
    <string name="spinner_title">Area</string>
    <string-array name="services">
        <item>Plumbing</item>
        <item>Painting</item>
        <item>Maintenance</item>
        <item>LED Tv</item>
        <item>New connection</item>
        <item>Electricals</item>
        <item>Installation</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="places">
        <item>80 Feet Road</item>
        <item>Alagappan Nagar</item>
        <item>Alagar Kavil Road</item>
        <item>Amman Sannathi Street</item>
        <item>Anaiyur</item>
        <item>Andalpuram</item>
        <item>Anna Nagar</item>
        <item>Anuppanadi</item>
        <item>Arappalayam</item>
        <item>Arasaradi</item>
        <item>Avaniyapuram</item>
        <item>Bibikulam</item>
        <item>Bypass Road</item>
        <item>Chinna Chokkikulam</item>
        <item>Chokikulam</item>
        <item>Dhanappa Mudali Street</item>
        <item>East Avani Moola Street</item>
        <item>East Marret Street</item>
        <item>East Masi Street</item>
        <item>East Veli Street</item>
        <item>Ellis Nagar</item>
        <item>Gandhi Nagar</item>
        <item>Gnanavolivupuram</item>
        <item>Goripalayam</item>
        <item>Jaihindpuram</item>
        <item>K.K. Nagar</item>
        <item>K.Pudur</item>
        <item>Kaka Thoppu Street</item>
        <item>Kalavasal</item>
        <item>Kamarajar Salai</item>
        <item>Kansamettu Street</item>
        <item>Kochadai</item>
        <item>Kodikulam</item>
        <item>Koodal Nagar</item>
        <item>Krishnapuram Colony</item>
        <item>Krishnarayar Tank Road</item>
        <item>Lakshmipuram</item>
        <item>Mahaboopalayam</item>
        <item>Manjanakara Street</item>
        <item>Mattuthavani</item>
        <item>Melakkal Road</item>
        <item>Melur Road</item>
        <item>Munichalai Road</item>
        <item>Naicker New Street</item>
        <item>Narayanapuram</item>
        <item>Narimedu</item>
        <item>Nethaji Road</item>
        <item>New Mahalipatti Road</item>
        <item>New Natham Road</item>
        <item>North Chitrai Street</item>
        <item>North Masi Street</item>
        <item>North Veli Street</item>
        <item>Othakadai</item>
        <item>Palace Road</item>
        <item>Palanganatham</item>
        <item>Pasumalai</item>
        <item>Ponmeni</item>
        <item>PT Rajan Road</item>
        <item>S S Colony</item>
        <item>Sathya Sai Nagar</item>
        <item>Sellur</item>
        <item>Sellur Road</item>
        <item>Shenoy Nagar</item>
        <item>Simmakkal</item>
        <item>South Avani Moola Street</item>
        <item>South Gate</item>
        <item>South Marret Street</item>
        <item>South Masi Street</item>
        <item>South Veli Street</item>
        <item>SS Colony</item>
        <item>Subramaniapuram</item>
        <item>Surya Nagar</item>
        <item>Tallakulam</item>
        <item>Tamil Sangam Road</item>
        <item>Theni Main Road</item>
        <item>Town Hall Road</item>
        <item>TPK Road</item>
        <item>TVS Nagar</item>
        <item>Uthangudi</item>
        <item>Vakkil New Street</item>
        <item>Velmurugan Nagar</item>
        <item>Vengalakadai Street</item>
        <item>Vilangudi</item>
        <item>Villapuram</item>
        <item>Virattipathu</item>
        <item>Visalakshipuram Main Road</item>
        <item>Vishwanathapuram</item>
        <item>West Avani Moola Street</item>
        <item>West Masi Street</item>
        <item>West Perumal Maistry Street</item>
        <item>West Tower Street</item>
        <item>West Vadampokki Street</item>
        <item>West Veli Street</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="support1_title">How can I book service online?</string>
    <string name="support1_desc">Go to home and select the service you want to book. Add any item to your cart, select the address where you want the service and schedule it according to your convenience. After that, just pay and book the service and we will take care of the rest</string>
    <string name="support2_title">How to contact INSES Partner for my booking?</string>
    <string name="support2_desc">Although you should not need to call your INSES Partner for your booking, but still in case you need to, Use the below CALL US to contact INSES Partner. You will redirect to INSES Partner. He will help you.</string>
    <string name="support3_title">What happens if I am not satisfied with the quality of service?</string>
    <string name="support3_desc">In an unfortunate case where you are not satisfied with the quality of service, we will happy to assist you and understand your query in detail. Please use the below options to reach out to us</string>
</resources>